迈克 · 诺斯: 我们马上就可以看出这是一个很大的数字，太冗长了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We can see right away
that this is a lot, this is verbose.
我们必须指定电子邮件和姓名。
We have to specify email and name.
这句话已经出现三次了，对吧？
Those words are here three times, right?
一次定义类型，一次在构造函数签名和
Once to define the type,
once in the constructor signature and
然后当我们从函数参数传递到实例时。
then as we pass from function
arguments onto the instance.
因此，TypeScript 为此提供了一个称为参数属性的快捷方式。
So TypeScript has a shortcut for
this called Parameter Properties.
我们来看看这个。
And we're gonna look at that.
但与此同时，我们必须引入这些访问修饰符关键字。
But at the same time, we have to
introduce these access modifier keywords.
所以你会看到这是三个选择之一,
So you'll see these as
being one of three choices,
公共场所，这是你习惯的，对吗？
public, which is what you're used to,
right?
我们在 JavaScript 中唯一拥有的东西是公共的，并且是带有下划线的公共的,
The only thing we have in JavaScript is
public, and public with an underscore,
也就是说你用这个很丢脸，但这还是公开的。
which means shame on you for
using that, but it's still public.
Protected 允许实例和子类的任何实例查看它。
Protected allows the instance, and
any instance of a subclass, to see it.
在 private 中，意味着只有那个类型可以看到它，只有那个类可以。
In private, means only that type
can see it, only that class.
即使是子类也不能看到私有方法或私有字段。
Even a subclass won't be able to see
a private method or private field.
下面是这些参数属性的一个例子。
So, here is an example of
these parameter properties.
不幸的是，自动格式化让事情变得不那么理想。
And unfortunately, the auto formatting
kinda makes things less than ideal.
这里和我们之前的例子的区别是,
So, the difference here
from our previous example,
很明显，有很多东西是不存在的。
obviously, there are a lot of
things that are not present.
但是通过在构造函数之前添加访问修饰符关键字
But through adding an access modifier
keyword before our constructor's
我们可以创建与之前相同的设置。
arguments, we can create the equivalent
setup to what we had before.
事实上，我甚至在这里添加了一些东西
In fact, I have even added
a little something here, and
这是第二个字段的默认值。
that is the default value for
the second field.
这意味着我在构造函数中引入一个参数
So this means I take an argument
in my constructor and
类似于同名字段的参数应该存在于实例中。
a parameter like a field of the same
name should exist on the instance.
当你在构造函数中收到它的时候,
And when you receive
it in the constructor,
你应该把它放在实例上。
you should place it on the instance.
我要用同样的例子来说服你们。
And I'm gonna convince you of this
by taking this exact same example.
我只是要删除界面。
I'm just gonna remove the interface.
我要把它放到打字稿游乐场
And I'm gonna put it into
the TypeScript Playground so
我们可以看到它编译的 JavaSscript。
we can see the JavaSscript
that it compiles to.
迈克 · 诺斯: 去掉界面。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
get rid of the interface.
所以，在右边，我知道我们在这里被切断，但是
So, on the right side,
I know we're getting cut off here but
我们可以看到，如果电子邮件是，这是未定义的，void 0是未定义的,
we can see that if the email is,
this is undefined, void 0 is undefined,
如果电子邮件没有定义，用默认值初始化它。
if the email is undefined,
initialize it with the default value.
然后我们将接收名称作为函数参数,
And then we will receive
name as a function argument,
我们把它放在实例上，电子邮件也一样。
we put it on the instance,
same with email.
这是实际上在构造函数主体中的注释。
And then this is the comment that was
actually in the body of our constructor.
所以你可以在构造函数中看到任何你自定义的东西,
So you can see anything in your
constructor that you do custom,
在参数到字段的映射完成之后会发生。
would happen after all of this mapping
from parameters to fields has taken place.
这是一个非常好的方便，因为它允许我们这样做
This is a really nice convenience
because it allows us to do this common
我们想把一些东西传递给构造函数,
thing where we want to pass
some stuff into a constructor,
收集田地，这样就不那么冗长了。
get the fields,
it makes it a lot less verbose.
请注意，如果我们要使这个受保护，这意味着外部
Note that if we were to make this
protected, which means the outside
在与 ParamPropContract 实例交互时,
world when interacting with
an instance of ParamPropContract,
它看不到这片区域。
it wouldn't be able to see this field.
所以，我们仍然可以把它作为一个论点，但是
So, we still can receive
it as an argument, but
你不能从外面进入。
you're not going to be able to
access it from the outside.
迈克 · 诺斯: 只是路过这里的一些无意义的领域,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Just passing
in some nonsense fields here,
毫无意义的价值观。
nonsense values rather.
在这下面你可以看到我们只有名字，而以前,
Down here you can see we only have
access to name whereas before,
我们两个都有权限。
we have access to both.
这就是公开和保护的区别。
So that's the difference in
making it public or protected.
你们会注意到我这么做的另一个后果
And you'll note that another
consequence of me making it
我在这里得到一个错误说类错误
protected was I get an error up
here saying the class incorrectly
实现的接口有电子邮件。
implements the interface HasEmail.
有人能猜测为什么会发生这种错误吗？
Can anyone make a guess as to
why this error is happening?
显然，字段是存在的，但为什么打字稿会反对呢？
Clearly, the field is there, but
why might TypeScript be objecting?
发件人1: 电子邮件不可见。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Email's not visible.
迈克 · 诺斯: 电子邮件是看不见的。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Email's not visible.
你希望这个类的实例是 HasEmail,
You expect the instance of
this class to be a HasEmail,
意思是你可以访问名字和电子邮件。
meaning you can access name and
you can access email.
这就是 HasEmail 的含义。
That's what it means to be a HasEmail.
所以你并没有真正遵循一个界面，除非那些东西允许你这么做
So you're not really conforming to an
interface unless the things that allow you
是公开的，从外面就可以看到。
to conform to it are public and
visible from the outside.
迈克 · 诺斯: 现在这个错误消失了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
now the error goes away.
Mike North: 所以 class 字段可以有初始化器。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
class fields can have initializers.
如果你想要一个 ParamProp 初始化器,
If you want a ParamProp initializer,
和函数参数一样,
just do the same thing you would do for
function arguments,
因为它是一个函数参数，就是它所在的位置，对吗？
cuz it is a function argument,
that's kind of where it lives, right?
这就是 email 字段的默认值。
So that's the default value for
the email field.
但是如果你有一些属性，这些属性不是你可以用作参数的东西
But if you have properties that are not
things that you take in as arguments to
一个构造函数，在这个例子中，年龄，你可以在顶部看到,
a constructor, in this case, age,
which you can see up at the top,
你可以用 JavaScript 做同样的事情。
you can just do the same thing
you would do in JavaScript.
这实际上是一个默认值。
This effectively is a default value.
如果它不像这里的构造函数那样以某种方式设置。
If it is not in some way set like
within the constructor here.
所以如果我在这里做像35岁，现在这样永远不会发挥作用。
So if in here I were to do like age = 35,
now like this will never come into play.
只有当它还没有被初始化的时候，它才会被初始化
It is only initialized with
that if it has not yet
已经被初始化了。
been initialized up until that point.
我们在哪里可以看到这方面的证据？
Where do we see evidence of that?
基本上就会变成这样。
It's basically gonna turn
into this right here.
如果它没有定义，初始化它。
If it's undefined, initialize it.
迈克 · 诺斯: 你有问题吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Did you have a question?
演讲者2: 是的，如果你给它一个默认值，它能推断出类型吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, does it infer
the type, if you give it a default?
迈克 · 诺斯: 是的，因为它是一个,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Yes, because it's a,
和变量一样的规则，你给它初始值,
kinda same rules as a variable,
you're giving it its initial value,
所以它会尽最大努力合理地推测。
and so it will do the best it can to
make a reasonable guess of the type.
现在你需要注意的是，这是一个字符串还是
Now the one thing you'd want to be careful
of is if this could be a string or
可以是一个数字，你把它初始化为一个数字，你需要具体
could be a number and you initialize it to
a number, you're going to have to specific
你会故意扩大字体，包括字符串的可能性。
that you'll deliberately widen the type
to include the possibility of a string.
因此，它将做出它通常的猜测，这是正确的。
So it will make its usual guess and
rightly so.
我可以把它拿走，它仍然是第号。
I can take that away, and
it'll still be number.
Mike North: 还有另外一个适用于访问修饰符的东西
&gt;&gt; Mike North: There's one other thing
that kind of fits into access modifier
关键字，虽然它不是真的在可见性方面的访问。
keywords, although it's not really
about access in terms of visibility.
你也可以做只读。
You could also do readonly.
从类型检查的角度来看，这会让你大喊大叫
And that, from a type checking
perspective, will yell at you for
尝试网站，其中您试图写到这个值。
attempted sites where you
are trying to write to this value.
别自欺欺人了,
Don't fool yourself, through,
因为这个库可能会有 JavaScript 的使用者。
because there may be JavaScript
consumers of this library.
这根本不能阻止对这个值的权利。
And this does nothing at all in terms of
actually preventing rights to this value.
它就像一个为使用字体信息的人租用的东西。
It is just like a renting thing for
people using type information.
所以，我会偶尔使用这个但是
So, I'll use this once in while but
请注意，不是每个人都使用类型信息。
just be advised that not
everyone uses type information.
这只是一张支票，对吗？
And this is just making a check, right?